const e={sections:[{header:{text:"Choose the right verb form in the past simple tense"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:"Your cake (to be) delicious!",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was",2:"were",3:"be",4:"are"}},{type:"test",question:"We (to buy) a car last spring.",rightAnswerIds:["2"],answers:{1:"brought",2:"bought",3:"buyed",4:"boutghted"}},{type:"test",question:"Last year I (to be) in London.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was",2:"am",3:"were",4:"is"}},{type:"test",question:"We (to visit) our relatives three months ago.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"visited",2:"visiting",3:"visits",4:"visitid"}},{type:"test",question:"I (to cook) dinner yesterday.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"cooked",2:"cooking",3:"cake",4:"cook"}},{type:"test",question:"My grandmother (not to water) the flowers in the garden yesterday.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"did not water",2:"not watered",3:"watered not",4:"did not watered"}},{type:"test",question:"His brothers (not to do) homework last week.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"did not do",2:"did not",3:"did not did",4:"do not did"}},{type:"test",question:"We (not to go) to the library yesterday.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"did not go",2:"notgoed",3:"do not go",4:"did not goed"}},{type:"test",question:"She (not to tell) me a secret yesterday.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"did not tell",2:"told not",3:"did not telled",4:"did not told"}},{type:"test",question:"They (not to work) last week.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"did not work",2:"not worked",3:"did not worked",4:"work not did"}},{type:"test",question:"Mary (to be) at school yesterday.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was",2:"be",3:"was",4:"beed"}},{type:"test",question:"Bob's parents (to be) at work last Saturday.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"were",2:"are",3:"be",4:"was"}},{type:"test",question:"Two years ago Tom and Meg (to be) students.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"were",2:"are",3:"be",4:"was"}},{type:"test",question:"Pete (to give) me a book last week.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"gave",2:"given",3:"gived",4:"givd"}},{type:"test",question:"Tom (to play) football yesterday.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"played",2:"play did",3:"playing",4:"plaed"}}]}]};export{e as default};
